winbet.bg 2014-10-19

# WinBet Help

## Win Again in regards to the privacy for all user.

All information in this **site** is free and does not require any personal information to be browsed.

## Cookies and Browsing

Win Again uses not cookies to store personal date of users or there browsing information. Any cookies that come from this website are are the responsibly of that casinos privacy policy and not Win Again. Visitors do not need to allow the cookies to be stored on there computer if they should to not. Access still shall be granted.

## Email

We don't solicit or spam and have many instruments and tools in out disposal to avoid any form of spam. All emails acquired thru are newsletter, are not given out to any 3rd party and will never be sold. No emails will ever be made public before given prior consent from the 3rd party. All emails send out by or received by Win Again are legally binding.

## Casino Information Sharing

We do not collect any information of the browsers of this site. If any information is gathered from visitors that's is only if the user consents to such. We do not sell, rent, or give out any private information ever unless subpoenaed law enforcement agency.

## Privacy Policy Changes

Win Again reserves the right to change, modify or delete any form of the privacy policy at any time but will normally give 24hrs for any changes to be made courtesy to are users.

## Credit Card Info

We do not accept, ask or store any credit card info, if in the future credit card info is requested we will not store or save it on are servers.

 _If any privacy policy conditions is not being met or needs to change, email us: privacy@win-again.com_
